Wealth, Fame, Power.
Gold Roger, the King of the Pirates,
attained this and everything
else the world had to offer,
and his dying words drove
countless souls to the seas.
You want my treasure?
You can have it.
I left everything I gathered
together in one place.
Now you just have to find it.
These words lured men to
the Grand Line in pursuit
of dreams greater than
they'd ever dared to imagine.
This is the time known
as the Great Pirate Era.
Come aboard and bring along
all your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything
that we're looking for.
One Piece.
Compass left behind,
it'll only slow us down.
Your heart will be your guide,
raise the sails and take the helm.
That legendary place that
the end of the map reveals.
Is only legendary till
someone proves it real.
Through it all, through
all the trouble and times.
Through the heartache
and through the pain.
Know that I will be there to stand by you.
Just like I know you'll stand by me.
So come aboard and bring along.
All your hopes and dreams.
Together we will find everything.
That we're looking for.
There's always room for you.
If you wanna be my friend.
We are, we are on a cruise.
We are.
You're going to be king
of the pirates right?
you must be completely
out of your rubbery mind.
Do you have any idea what that means?
yeah when he first told me it was shocking
but he's Completely
serious that's how he is.
i suppose.
Here's what i promised you there's three i
couldn't tell which was
yours so i just took
all Of them all of them belong to me i use
sentoryu the three swords
style just know that if
you Fight with me now
you'll be a government
defying villain so it's
either that or you're
left out here And killed by the Marines
execution style what are
you the son of the devil?
it doesn't matter Because
if I don't choose your side
I'll just end up dead on
these sticks so let's do it.
So you're finally gonna join my
crew this is the best thing ever.
You quit celebrating already
and get these ropes off me?
what the what is he?
Bullets just bounced right off him!
Straw Hat's no ordinary
human like the rest of us.
He must have eaten one
of those devil fruits
that we've heard all those rumors about.
Devil Fruit?
The hidden treasure of the sea!
Come on, hurry!
They got these things on here tight!
Come on, quit screwing around!
It doesn't matter what abilities they
have, all who oppose me are executed!
If the guns won't work, we jump! Up!
That's funny, the nuts got
tighter instead of looser.
Give me one of my damn swords now!
Luffy, look!
Roronoa Zoro!
Oh wow, that's so cool!
Make one move and you die.
He's scary!
Today I officially become a
criminal, having fought the Marines.
So I'll become a pirate.
That I can promise you.
But I want you to know one thing.
While I'm with you, the only thing I
dedicate myself to is fulfilling my ambition.
Which is?
To be nothing less than the
world's greatest swordsman.
If somewhere along the way
I have to give that up,
then I want you to accept responsibility.
After which, you get to apologize to me.
The world's greatest swordsman.
Sounds pretty good.
The King of the Pirates wouldn't have
any less than the best on his crew.
Big talker.
From this point on, no matter
if I'm a criminal or not,
I will spread the name
Zoro throughout the world.
What are you standing there frozen for?
I want you to kill all
three of them right now!
You might want to duck!
Gum-Gum!
Yes!
You knocked them all down!
Wanna tell me what you are?
I'm just a guy who ate the Gum-Gum fruit.
What's the Gum-Gum fruit?
A rubber person?
It looks like he does have
the Devil Fruit powers.
Captain, we don't stand
a chance against them.
Yeah, just look at them!
They're insane!
We couldn't even take on Zoro by himself!
This is a direct order.
Every marine that just spouted weakness,
pull your gun out and shoot yourself.
I can't do anything with
weak soldiers but babies.
This will be easy.
Rankless lowlife bums!
You have no right to defy my superiority!
I am Marine Captain X-Hand Morgan!
And I'm Luffy!
Nice to meet ya!
Look! He's been hit!
You're right!
Now die!
I don't think so!
The captain's getting bubbled out there.
It's embarrassing.
Call yourself a marine, but you
destroyed my friend Kobe's dream!
Straw Hat!
Stop right there!
Look at what I got!
Are you stupid or something?
I said stop!
If you would pay attention to me, I have
a hostage here you might want to look at!
Helmepo's crazy!
Hey.
Huh?
If you value your Squad little
friend's life, you won't move a muscle!
I'm serious!
Why move and I'll shoot him, I swear!
Wolf, listen!
Don't let anything that happens
to me stop you no matter what!
Even if I die!
Of course, you got it!
You hear that, you big idiot?
Koby is ready to die by your hand.
Don't you move!
I said don't move or I'll shoot!
I swear it!
Luffy!
Gum-Gum!
Time's up!
For I am Fearless Marine
Captain Axe and Morgan!
Daddy, hurry up and kill him already!
Hey, stop!
Nice one!
Thank you.
I'm just doing my job, Captain.
Captain Morgas has been beaten!
Unbelievable!
Those guys are unreal!
If there's anyone else who wants to step
forward to fight us, then do it now.
We're free!
Finally!
The train is over!
Such a glorious day!
That's weird.
Looks like they're all happy
that their captain was beaten.
They must have been afraid of him
for a long time before we showed up!
Zoro! Are you okay? What's wrong?
I'm just... hungry.
I am stuffed!
Having not eaten for three weeks, I was
ready to gnaw up through my bootstraps!
I can't believe you're
finished, Lightweight.
How the hell can you have a bigger appetite
than a guy who hasn't eaten in weeks?
It just tastes too good, I guess.
Right, Colby?
Yeah, it's great.
Thanks for fixing it for us. My pleasure.
After all, you guys did save the town.
You're the most amazing man I've ever met!
Yeah, I am, I know.
I'll be more amazing when I'm king of
the pirates and I have the One Piece.
Oh, and the best crew on the seas.
Luffy, where are you and your crew
planning on traveling when you leave here?
You mean it's not obvious?
We're headed straight for the Grand Line!
No!
Have you completely lost your mind?
You have two crew members!
There's no way you're equipped
ahead of the Grand Line, Luffy!
I've heard about it, but I never
knew it was such an awful place.
It's worse than you think!
You know that this world
has two oceans, I'm sure.
There is an enormous land mass
that cuts across both of them.
This is called the Red Line.
Legend tells of a town that sits
dead center on the Red Line.
The Grand Line is set to cut
through this town at a right
angle and stretch all the way
around the rest of the world.
The story goes on to say that Gold Roger,
the King of the Pirates, had once obtained
everything this world had to offer.
Before he died, he said that he left the
great One Piece treasure at this location.
Ever since, pirates have
set sail for the Grand Line.
Today,
the place is nothing but a battlefield,
and some even call it the Pirate Graveyard.
I heard stories about it
from people passing through.
The customers say that no
one who has ever entered
the Grand Line comes
out of that place alive.
Which is really too bad, because that's
where the One Piece is said to be?
and that's exactly where we're going.
I guess we have to live with it. No!
You can't agree!
What do you care?
You're not going with us, are you?
No, but I still worry.
Is it so wrong to care
about the two of you?
Luffy and I haven't known each
other for years or anything,
but I'd still consider him a friend.
Wouldn't you say? Of course!
We may have to part ways,
but we'll always be friends.
When I was just a little
kid, I never had any friends,
much less anyone who would
bother fighting on my behalf.
So I always tried my hardest
never to fight for anything.
But the two of you have taught me a
lesson I could never learn on my own,
how to live for what I believe in!
So I've decided to make my
one childhood dream a reality,
and I'm going to join the Marines!
Then don't you think you should be a
little more concerned with your situation?
I mean, you did spend two
years in Alvita's pirate ship,
even if you were nothing
but her cabin boy.
The Marines' information
gathering is top-notch.
They'll find out about your time
with Alvida, and you'll never join.
I never thought of that.
Hey, you there!
We heard that you fellas
are actually pirates.
Is this rumor true?
Right, and I just added the
first member to my crew.
So pretty much the whole
thing just became official.
We appreciate everything you
did to save our town from
that horrible tyrant who
terrorized us all for so long.
However,
now that we know that you're pirates,
we cannot sit idly by and watch
you go about your business.
Therefore, you and your crew will
need to leave this town immediately.
But out of respect for what you've done,
we will not report you to headquarters.
Are you crazy?
How do you find the
nerve to talk like that?
Before these pirates came along, you
guys were as scared of Borgen as we were.
Without them, we'd still
be under his reign.
We owe them our lives.
Well, time to go.
Thanks for all of the food, lady.
Hey, wait a second.
You're leaving already?
Yeah.
Aren't you part of the crew as well?
Well, I...
Hold it.
Is he with you or what?
What I can tell you is what he's
been busy doing up to this point.
Mulfi, you wouldn't!
Yeah, there was this
fantastically fat pirate lady.
I think her name was Alvida.
Mofi!
If they find out I ran with the pirate
crew, I'll never join the marine.
She carried around this
huge iron club, and boy,
she was the nastiest looking
woman I've ever seen.
For two years, this wimpy kid was her
own private cabin boy. Please stop.
You can't do this.
Mofi, no!
No!
Now that was a dumb move!
Bastard!
Get out of here now!
We can't have you pirates ripping up
this town any more than you already have,
you hear me?
Enough.
You made your point.
Now let him fall to the ground.
It's obvious you're not Gourmet?
So stop badgering the poor kid!
and take your leave of
our town this instant!
That was on purpose?
Luffy did that just to help me out.
He worked me up and got me so mad that I'd
hit him and look like
I wasn't on his side.
Even at the very end of our journey together,
I wound up continuing to rely on him.
I couldn't do anything for myself.
Nothing's changed for me at all.
I am such an idiot!
Sir!
Please, sir! Please,
you have to let me join
the Marines I'll clean
and scrub and do any chores
that you'd like me to.
I'll do anything to become a Marine!
Lieutenant, I can't say
I fully trust this kid?
I wouldn't be against the
idea if there weren't clear
cases of certain Marines
actually being pirate spies.
I say we should conduct
a background check first.
No matter what you say, I am a
man who will become a Marine!
Hmm.
I can't tell you how many of our comrades
have been killed by
pirates over the years.
This is a big step you're taking. So?
Permission to join granted.
Sir!
That was a thin act you put on back there.
I wouldn't be surprised if
they see right through it.
Kobe should be able to
handle the rest on his own.
I have faith in him.
It is a fitting way to leave this place.
Unable to turn back because
everyone here hates us now.
Very pirate-like.
Yeah, it sure is. Buffy!
I can never thank you enough!
You've done more for me
than anyone ever has!
I've never heard of a marine
thanking a pirate before.
That's one for the history books.
We'll meet again, Kobe!
Someday! Bye, Luffy.
Hope to see you again someday!
All hands salute!
See ya!
That's a good friend you have there.
Men,
seeing as our current salute
is in violation of marine law,
we will all go without
food for three days.
Do we all understand this?
Yes, sir!
Now, let's go!
It's time for us to set our
heading for the Grand Line!
As a kid, I never stopped.
Searching for a great treasure!
I had a map in my mind.
That I knew would lead me.
I had to find my way to that place!
Before someone could beat me.
The promised land was in my grasp.
And I wouldn't let go!
La la la la?
My only dream.
La la la la la!
I won't stop chasing
it until it comes true!
But if the world ever changes,
I call out your name!
We return to the time when
everything's the same.
As long as I'm with you,
my memories won't fade!
Waiting for that one true dream?